# Faisal Arshed

# Software Engineer github.com/farshed mail@farshed.me (+92) 309 6855375

Full Stack Engineer with 3+ years of experience. I enjoy working in small teams and having a high impact on the product from design to delivery. Interested in roles that offer ample opportunities for technical growth beyond my current expertise.

## Work Experience

Jul 2022 - Present

#### Senior Software Engineer

SmashCloud

- Collaborated on engineering for a Fortune Global 500 venture in a leading role
- Implemented new features for a tenant turnover management system used by some of the top student housing owners and managers across North America

Mar 2021 - Jun 2022

### Software Engineer

Pursue Today

- Developed pribox.io, acting as the sole engineer for majority of its MVP stage
- Developed automated planning and job scheduling services and closely worked with SMTP and IMAP protocols

Sep 2020 - Apr 2021

### Senior Engineer

BookOtto

- Prototyped and developed the flagship MVP using React Native and GraphQL
- Helped create and maintain the AWS backend and DevOps infrastructure
- Developed the Cribfox web app using React and AWS

Mar 2019 - Dec 2019

#### **React Native Developer**

MoneyWhere

- Developed core fintech MVP using React Native and Node.js
- Implemented a virtual currency system, payments, geolocation services and advanced map capabilities

#### Education

2016 - 2020

### **BS in Computer Science**

PMAS University of Arid Agriculture

#### Skills

JavaScrip	ot	React	Next.js	Rea	act Nativ	ve	Nod	e.js	A۱	WS
GraphQL	ľ	1ongoDB	PostgreSQL		Rust		Dart		Flutter	